<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mateus Felipe</title><link>http://mateusfccp.me/en/</link><description>Recent content on Mateus Felipe</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>pt-br</language><copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://mateusfccp.me/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Quickly deploying a personal website with Hugo and Docker</title><link>http://mateusfccp.me/en/posts/docker-and-hugo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://mateusfccp.me/en/posts/docker-and-hugo/</guid><description>Introduction Making a personal website is a trivial task. There are plenty options out there, from total newbies options, like Wix, to more robust (and, in this case, with a questionable quality), like Wordpress. However, if you want greater flexibility, it&amp;rsquo;s usual to appeal to more technical solutions. Even so, it seems to be a overengineering to waste your time dealing with routes, middlewares, HTTP requests or any other technical aspect that you probably don&amp;rsquo;t want to deal when making a simple personal website, even if you have the know-how.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>http://mateusfccp.me/en/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://mateusfccp.me/en/about/</guid><description>22, Theologian. Has been programming for 13 years, specializing himself, mainly, on PHP and correlated technology (Wordpress, Laravel). However, constantly deals with other technologies, like Python, Rust, go, Reason, Ecmascript, and ocassionaly plays with Elm, Elixir, Ruby, Hack, C, C++, C#, Dart, among others. Currently works autonomously as a web developer, and courses postgraduate studies (lato sensu) on Biblical Theology.</description></item></channel></rss>